[Music]
hey thought I'd show how you get help so
if you get stuck on one of the things
that you're doing by yourself on tinker
or if you're get stuck on the projects
we do together the way you get help is
you go to our website connecting with
code close that and then the camp page
is where the office hours are at the
office hours are every camp day so
that's Monday through Friday May 18
through 20 second for this week and then
there's sometimes next week and the way
it works is we have rules on students
I'm going to host some of them some
other students roasting others well
we've got four hours every day where you
can click to ask for help and so you can
see the the times listed here so if it's
Monday through Friday one of the camp
days what you need to do is you just
need to click these links and then
follow the rabbit trail that it takes
you all right but that will take you
into a zoom meeting and you'll see
people at the end of it into that tunnel
that are ready to help you with any kind
of problems that you've got
[Music]
you